(Sheldon:)Amy.
Angry Amy?
(Amy(on skype):)What?
(Sheldon:)I've been thinking about what happened,
and I hope this gift will make things better.
(Amy:)Star Trek DVDs?
(Amy:)Why would I want this?
(Sheldon:)First of all, you're welcome.
(Sheldon:)Furthermore, not being familiar
with Wil Wheaton's body of work...
(Sheldon:)...there was no way for you to know
you were being rude to a national treasure.
Get ready for 130 hours of "I told you so."
(Sheldon:)Fine, I'll just tell you what happens.
Episode one, "Encounter at Farpoint."
(Sheldon:)Fade in.
(Sheldon:)The new Enterprise heads out
on its maiden voyage...
(Sheldon:)...to contact the Bandi people of Deneb IV.
(Sheldon:)Enter Wesley Crusher,
played by my buddy...